{
   "name":"quiz4",
   "que0":[
      {
         "question":"How should you feel after you make your first dollar?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Ecstatic! This is the first time you made money on your own!",
            "b":"Eh, it's only a dollar."
         },
         "answer":"a"
      }
   ],
   "que1":[
      {
         "question":"Are you Broke or Poor?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Broke",
            "b":"Poor"
         },
         "answer":"a"
      }
   ],
   "que2":[
      {
         "question":"Why is it important to make your first dollar?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Because now I can buy cool things to impress others!",
            "b":"More money is always good",
            "c":"The reason it is important is now I know if I can make $1, I can make whatever I need if I put in the effort"
         },
         "answer":"c"
      }
   ],
   "que3":[
      {
         "question":"Are you implementing the knowledge inside these videos?",
         "options":{
            "a":"yes",
            "b":"no"
         },
         "answer":"a"
      }
   ],
   "que4":[
      {
         "question":"What items should you sell?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Anything as long as you get it for free",
            "b":"Anything that you know sells well"
         },
         "answer":"b"
      }
   ],
   "que5":[
      {
         "question":"What makes you rich?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Unfair Advantages",
            "b":"Shitcoins"
          },
         "answer":"a"
      }
   ],
   "que6":[
      {
         "question":"What do you do if you don't have craigslist in your country?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Give up",
            "b":"Search for alternatives"
         },
         "answer":"b"
      }
   ],
   "que7":[
      {
         "question":"What do I do If I Don\u2019t Have A Car?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Give up",
            "b":"Go to the Millionaire Access general chat and complain this doesn't work.",
            "c":"Use your parent's,friend's,rent or UBER. There is always a way."
         },
         "answer":"c"
      }
   ],
   "que8":[
      {
         "question":"What is flipping?",
         "options":{
            "a":"just a way to make money.",
            "b":"Taking a free item or item you get for less and selling for profit.",
            "c":"Clocking in for a paycheck."
         },
         "answer":"b"
      },
      {
         "question":"Should I post to only one platform or many?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Nah just one is good.",
            "b":"I should post to many as it increases the likelihood of who will buy my items."
         },
         "answer":"b"
      }
   ],
   "que9":[
      {
         "question":"Why is it important to have good pictures/titles for your products?",
         "options":{
            "a":"To make it look fancy.",
            "b":"To make your products more attractive for your potential buyers."
         },
         "answer":"b"
      },
      {
         "question":"Should I post to only one platform or many?",
         "options":{
            "a":"I should post to many as it increases the likelihood of who will buy my items.",
            "b":"Nah just one is good."
         },
         "answer":"a"
      }
   ],
   "que10":[
      {
         "question":"Are you going to implement the Flipping Course?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Yes, I'm ready to make my first $100"
         },
         "answer":"a"
      }
   ]
}